# Lucas Carneiro



lucas.carneiro.dev@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/lucas-gabriel96



55 41 999550-3436



https://www.linkedin.com/in/lucas-gabriel96/

### Summary

As a Full Stack developer focused on Front End I have been working with Web development since 2016, during this period I participated in building and maintaining several applications from different segments, financial, educational, and e-commerce. In that time as a developer, I've always been challenged to learn new technologies and generate good results in a short time. My main stack is Javascript | TypeScript, React, NextJs, Jest, RecoilJs, Apollo, GRAPHQL | REST, and NodeJs | C#, at the moment I've been studying Docker and AWS.

### **Experience**

#### ce Software Engineer Front End

Object Edge

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Working on international projects using English as a language main, I was part of a project where partner mechanics from the greater São Paulo can sell their automotive services in a marketplace to customers B2C and worked on building e-commerce for parts sales automotive, a project today with a large number of products registered and partnership with Bosch Brazil. I am currently working on an application configuration

Used Technologies: JavaScript | TypeScript, Reactjs, NextJs, RecoilJS, Jest, GRAPHQL, GIT, Storybook, Styled Components | Emotion, GIT, HTML5, CSS | SASS.

## Front End Developer

Mooveon

May 2021 - Sep 2021 (5 months)

Responsible for creating new Front End applications following faithfully prototypes in Figma and delivering the best solutions.

Used Technologies: C#, .NET MVC, SQL, GIT, JavaScript | TypeScript, Reactjs, Styled Components, Jquery, HTML5, CSS | SASS



## Full Stack Developer

Faculdade UNINA

Aug 2020 - Feb 2021 (7 months)

I worked mainly in the maintenance and creation of new modules of Internal system and college student environment.

Used Technologies: C#, .NET MVC, DDD, SQL, GIT, JavaScript, AngularJS, VueJS, Jquery, HTML5, CSS

## m Full Stack Developer

N&J Partners Consultoria

Aug 2018 - Jun 2020 (1 year 11 months)

I participated in the refactoring of the old system, ensuring high availability during the day, security in transactions and reliability in the values of

large financial transactions.

Used Technologies: C#, .NET MVC, DDD, SQL, GIT, JavaScript, AngularJS, Jquery, HTML5, CSS

## Front End Developer

Deal

Mar 2018 - Aug 2018 (6 months)

Allocated to clients, I participated in the creation and maintenance of a online vehicle auction.

Used Technologies: C#, .NET MVC, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML5, CSS

## **Web Developer**

Serdia Eletrônica Industrial

Oct 2016 - Jun 2017 (9 months)

Web development with PHP and support to the company's ERP users through internal and external calls.

Used Technologies: PHP, SQL, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML5, CSS

## Web Developer

Ibolt sys

Nov 2015 - Oct 2016 (1 year)

Web development using PHP and Desktop with Filemaker, also supporting users of the company's systems.

Used Technologies: PHP, SQL, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML5, CSS

#### **Education**

#### 

Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas, Tecnologia em Informática/Software 2016 - 2018

#### 

Técnico em Informática, Tecnologia em Informática/Software 2014 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Creating APIs with Node balta.io
- Javascript Fundamentals Erick Wendel Training and Consulting
- Learn to test JavaScript Applications Evergreen Treinamentos Fabio Vedovelli

## **Skills**

RecoilJS • Jest • Next.js • SQL • Git • React.js • CSS | SASS • Styled Components | Emotion • C# | .NET MVC • JavaScript | TypeScript